<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Pseudoyu</title>
    <link>https://www.hexarthur.com/en/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Pseudoyu</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Sep 2020 01:25:19 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.hexarthur.com/en/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>New iPad Air 4 (2020) Presence by Apple Inc.</title>
      <link>https://www.hexarthur.com/en/2020/09/18/new-ipad-air-4-2020-presence-by-apple-inc./</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Sep 2020 01:25:19 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hexarthur.com/en/2020/09/18/new-ipad-air-4-2020-presence-by-apple-inc./</guid>
      <description>E-Commerce Presence Look Around New iPad Air 4 (2020) Presence by Apple Inc. Website Link
The iPad Air 4 (2020) got shown off at Apple&amp;rsquo;s September event held on September 16. There is a specific designed website (mobile version included) for this product. I&amp;rsquo;d like to do an analysis towards this very impressive E-Commerce presence.
Apple iPad Air product line is mainly targeted to educators/students, staffs and kids/teenagers. So, the most premium features this new product wants to convey to customers is its fancy appearance and powerful A14 Bionic for creation, study and entertainment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>COMP7103 Topic 1 Introduction</title>
      <link>https://www.hexarthur.com/en/2020/09/18/comp7103-topic-1-introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Sep 2020 01:18:17 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hexarthur.com/en/2020/09/18/comp7103-topic-1-introduction/</guid>
      <description>COMP7103 Data Mining Topic 1 Introduction Decision-Support System (DSS)
 A decision-support system (DSS) is a system that assists decision makers to make important decisions for an organization or business KDD and data mining are important components in many DSS&amp;rsquo;s  Data and Knowledge
 Data  A collecion of facts about certain group of objects   Pattern  Certain characteristics of data that are frequently observed   Knowledge  Some general rules about the objects    Data Warehouse</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ICOM6012 Topic 2 The Big Picture</title>
      <link>https://www.hexarthur.com/en/2020/09/17/icom6012-topic-2-the-big-picture/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2020 10:18:09 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hexarthur.com/en/2020/09/17/icom6012-topic-2-the-big-picture/</guid>
      <description>ICOM6012 Internet Infrastructure Technologies Topic 2 The Big Picture The Internet: &amp;ldquo;nuts and bolts&amp;rdquo; view
 Billions of connected computing devices  Host = end system Running network apps Internet of things (IoT)   Packet switches  routers switchers   Communication links  Fiber, copper, radio, satellite Transmission rate: bandwidth   Networks  Collection of devices, routers, switches, links Managed by an organization   Internet: &amp;ldquo;network of networks&amp;rdquo;  Interconnected ISPs   Protocols  Control sending, receiving of messages   Internet standards  RFC: Requests for Comments IETF: Internet Engineering Task Force IEEE: Institute of Electronical &amp;amp; Electronic Engineering    The Internet: a &amp;ldquo;service&amp;rdquo; view</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ECOM6013 Topic 4 Website Design, Testing and Maintenance</title>
      <link>https://www.hexarthur.com/en/2020/09/16/ecom6013-topic-4-website-design-testing-and-maintenance/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2020 21:25:28 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hexarthur.com/en/2020/09/16/ecom6013-topic-4-website-design-testing-and-maintenance/</guid>
      <description>ECOM6013 E-Commerce Technologies Topic 4 Website Design, Testing and Maintenance Planing: The Systems Development Life Cycle
 Systems analysis/planing  Busisess objectives System functionalities Information requirements   Systems design Building the system Testing Implementation  Quality Consideration
 Navigation Accessibility Scalability Reliability Maintainability Usability Compatibility and interoperability Security Readability  In-House / Outsourcing (Hiring vendors to provide services)
 Build own / outsourcing Host own / outsourcing (preferred)  Implementation, Maintenance, and Optimization</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ECOM6013 Topic 3 E-Commerce Presence</title>
      <link>https://www.hexarthur.com/en/2020/09/16/ecom6013-topic-3-e-commerce-presence/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2020 20:25:28 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hexarthur.com/en/2020/09/16/ecom6013-topic-3-e-commerce-presence/</guid>
      <description>ECOM6013 E-Commerce Technologies Topic 3 E-Commerce Presence Image You E-Commerce Presence
 Idea  Mission Target audience Intended market space Strategic analysis Marketing matrix Development timeline Preliminary budget   About Money (e.g. Amazon&amp;rsquo;s e-commerce &amp;amp; Amazon&amp;rsquo;s AWS)  Business models Revenue models   About target audience  Demographics Lifestyle Consumption patterns &amp;hellip;   Marketplace Characteristics  Size Growth Demographics Structure   Content SWOT Analysis E-Commerce presence map Milestones Costs  Simple website: US$5000 Small startup: US$25,000 tp US$50,000 Large corporate website: US$100,000 + to millions    SWOT Analysis</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ECOM6013 Topic 2 Internet and E-Commerce Infrasture</title>
      <link>https://www.hexarthur.com/en/2020/09/16/ecom6013-topic-2-internet-and-e-commerce-infrasture/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2020 19:28:28 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hexarthur.com/en/2020/09/16/ecom6013-topic-2-internet-and-e-commerce-infrasture/</guid>
      <description>ECOM6013 E-Commerce Technologies Topic 2 Internet and E-Commerce Infrasture Internet
 Interconnected network of thousands of networks and hundreds of millions of computers Links businesses, educational institutions, government agencies, and individuals  World Wide Web (WWW)
 One of the internet&amp;rsquo;s most popular services Provides access to billions, possibly trillions, of Web pages  Evolution of Internet
 Innovation phase (1961 - 1974) Institutionalization phase (1975 - 1995) Commercialization Phase (1995 - present)  Packet Switching</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>COMP7404 Topic 1 Search</title>
      <link>https://www.hexarthur.com/en/2020/09/16/comp7404-topic-1-search/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2020 00:28:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hexarthur.com/en/2020/09/16/comp7404-topic-1-search/</guid>
      <description>COMP7404 Computational Intelligence and Machine Learning Topic 1 Search Types of Search
 Uninformed Search (Know nothing about the problem except definition) Informed Search (know something more like how close to the goal) Local Search (Randomly initilize a state and make it better, e.g. Deep Learning) Constraint Satisfaction Problems (Know more about the problem) Adversarial Search (have an opponent, e.g. chess, star craft game)  Is Search the same as Unsupervised/Supervised Learning?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ECO108 Topic 1 Ten Principles of Economics</title>
      <link>https://www.hexarthur.com/en/2020/09/10/eco108-topic-1-ten-principles-of-economics/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2020 09:28:12 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hexarthur.com/en/2020/09/10/eco108-topic-1-ten-principles-of-economics/</guid>
      <description>Introduction to Economics The word economy comes from the Greek work oikonomos, which means &amp;ldquo;one who manages a household&amp;rdquo;. Economics is the study of How society manages its scarce resources.
Topic 1 Ten Principles of Economics Principle 1: People Face Trade-Offs
One classic trade-off - &amp;ldquo;guns (national defense) and butter (consumer goods)&amp;rdquo;.
Another trade-off - efficiency and equality.
Principle 2: The Cost of Something Is What You Give Up to Get It</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ICOM6012 Topic 1 Overview</title>
      <link>https://www.hexarthur.com/en/2020/09/09/icom6012-topic-1-overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 20:22:09 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hexarthur.com/en/2020/09/09/icom6012-topic-1-overview/</guid>
      <description>ICOM6012 Internet Infrastructure Technologies Topic 1 Overview Internet&amp;rsquo;s Birthday: Sept. 2 or Oct. 29, 1969.
 ARPANET (1969 -)  TCP protocol in 1974 &amp;ldquo;Internet = Internetworking&amp;rdquo;   NSFNET (1986 -) The Internet (late 1980s)  Some Interesting Topics about Internet (More than Technical)
 Who controls the Internet? What is Net Neutrality? A TikTok Ban Is Overdue Zoom’s stock surges 41% after earnings beat, adding over $37 billion in market cap  Evolution of Computers</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Puma Goes Omni Case Study</title>
      <link>https://www.hexarthur.com/en/2020/09/08/puma-goes-omni-case-study/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 23:30:19 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hexarthur.com/en/2020/09/08/puma-goes-omni-case-study/</guid>
      <description>Puma Goes Omni About Puma Puma Official Website
A Fancy Presentation
Slogan: &amp;ldquo;Run The Streets. Do You.&amp;rdquo;
The third largest sportswear manufacture in the world. (2018)
The company was founded in 1948 by Rudolf Dassler.
Building a Centralize Website Restructuring Strategy
 Replacing multiple e-commerce sites on different platform Unifying content and product strategies Building multiple teams in different regions, separate tasks  Content Management System (CMS)
&amp;ldquo;Database software program specifically designed to manage structures, unstructured data and objects in a Website environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ECOM6013 Topic 1 Introduction to E-Commerce Technology</title>
      <link>https://www.hexarthur.com/en/2020/09/06/ecom6013-topic-1-introduction-to-e-commerce-technology/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2020 04:28:28 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hexarthur.com/en/2020/09/06/ecom6013-topic-1-introduction-to-e-commerce-technology/</guid>
      <description>ECOM6013 E-Commerce Technologies Topic 1 Introduction to E-Commerce Technology Discussion Topic #1: Puma Goes Omni
 What is the purpose of Puma&amp;rsquo;s content management systems? Why did Puma build a single centralized website rather than continue with multiple websites serving different countries and regions? [choosen] What social media sites does Puma use, and what do they contribute to Puma&amp;rsquo;s marketing effort?  Case Study
Alibaba Singles&amp;rsquo; Day 2019
Core E-Commerce Technologies  Introduction to E-Commerce Technology Internet and E-Commerce Infrasture E-Commerce Presence and Development Life Circle Web Design, Implementation and Testing Introduction to Mobile Commerce Internet and E-Commerce Commerce Electronic Payment Systems Cybercurrency, Bitcoin and Blockchain Emerging Technology &amp;amp; Cloud Computing and IoT Artificial Intelligence, Machine Learning and E-Commerce Trends  E-Commerce and Data Science</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PSY103 Topic 1 What Is Psychology</title>
      <link>https://www.hexarthur.com/en/2020/09/02/psy103-topic-1-what-is-psychology/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2020 12:48:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hexarthur.com/en/2020/09/02/psy103-topic-1-what-is-psychology/</guid>
      <description>Introduction to Psychology Topic 1 What Is Psychology Module 1.1 Psychologists&amp;rsquo; Goal General Points about Psychology
 It Depends Progress Depends on Good Measurement Confidence in the Conclusions Should Depend on the Strength of the Evidence  Major Philosophical Issues in Psychology
 Free Will versus Determinism The Mind-Brain Problem The Nature-Nurture Issue  What Psychologists Do
  Service Providers to Individuals
 Clinical Psychology Psychiatry Other Mental Health Professionals  Psychoanalysts Clinical social worker Counseling psychologists Forensic psychologists      Service Providers to Organizations</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dear Yu, Are you ready for 23?</title>
      <link>https://www.hexarthur.com/en/2020/06/06/dear-yu-are-you-ready-for-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hexarthur.com/en/2020/06/06/dear-yu-are-you-ready-for-23/</guid>
      <description>23岁的自白：去追寻意义 现在是2020年6月6日，我23岁了，这个年纪似乎是一个尴尬的存在，若按照人生阶段来界定，本科毕业已经是一年之前，而</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What To Eat - A WeChat Mini-Program Project</title>
      <link>https://www.hexarthur.com/en/2020/04/05/what-to-eat-a-wechat-mini-program-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2020 23:40:25 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hexarthur.com/en/2020/04/05/what-to-eat-a-wechat-mini-program-project/</guid>
      <description>What To Eat - A WeChat Mini-Program Project Source Code on Github
Development Details To be updated&amp;hellip;
WeChat Cloud-Dev Technology Utilized the WeChat official cloud-dev technology. There is no need to prepare/deploy our own server for the mini-program and save large images locally (exceeding the upload size limit of the mini program)
Screenshots QR-Code of this Mini-Program </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>