<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>programming on Pseudoyu</title>
    <link>https://www.hexarthur.com/en/tag/programming/</link>
    <description>Recent content in programming on Pseudoyu</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2020 21:30:11 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.hexarthur.com/en/tag/programming/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>COMP7404 Topic 2 Beyond Classical Search</title>
      <link>https://www.hexarthur.com/en/2020/10/04/comp7404-topic-2-beyond-classical-search/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2020 21:30:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hexarthur.com/en/2020/10/04/comp7404-topic-2-beyond-classical-search/</guid>
      <description>COMP7404 Computational Intelligence and Machine Learning Topic 2 Beyond Classical Search Planning vs Identification
 Planing: sequence of actions  The path to the goal is the important thing Paths have various costs, depths Heuristics to guide, frontier to keep backups   Identification: assignments to variables  The goal itself is important, not the path    Local Search can find solutions faster for specific types of identification problems</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>COMP7103 Topic 1 Introduction</title>
      <link>https://www.hexarthur.com/en/2020/09/18/comp7103-topic-1-introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Sep 2020 01:18:17 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hexarthur.com/en/2020/09/18/comp7103-topic-1-introduction/</guid>
      <description>COMP7103 Data Mining Topic 1 Introduction Decision-Support System (DSS)
 A decision-support system (DSS) is a system that assists decision makers to make important decisions for an organization or business KDD and data mining are important components in many DSS&amp;rsquo;s  Data and Knowledge
 Data  A collecion of facts about certain group of objects   Pattern  Certain characteristics of data that are frequently observed   Knowledge  Some general rules about the objects    Data Warehouse</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>COMP7404 Topic 1 Solving Problems by Searching</title>
      <link>https://www.hexarthur.com/en/2020/09/16/comp7404-topic-1-solving-problems-by-searching/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2020 00:28:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hexarthur.com/en/2020/09/16/comp7404-topic-1-solving-problems-by-searching/</guid>
      <description>COMP7404 Computational Intelligence and Machine Learning Topic 1 Solving Problems by Searching Types of Search
 Uninformed Search (Know nothing about the problem except definition) Informed Search (know something more like how close to the goal) Local Search (Randomly initilize a state and make it better, e.g. Deep Learning) Constraint Satisfaction Problems (Know more about the problem) Adversarial Search (have an opponent, e.g. chess, star craft game)  Is Search the same as Unsupervised/Supervised Learning?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>