<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Pseudoyu</title>
    <link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/zh/category/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Pseudoyu</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>zh</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 09:19:19 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.pseudoyu.com/zh/category/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A Look at Tik-Tok</title>
      <link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/zh/2020/10/16/a-look-at-tik-tok/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 09:19:19 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/zh/2020/10/16/a-look-at-tik-tok/</guid>
      <description>A Look at Tik-Tok Given there are many social media platforms already existing in US, what makes Tik-Tok so successful that it becomes a big enough threat to cause the US Government to act the way it did towards a commercial company (ignore political factors)? Economically, at about 2016, US tech giants such as Facebook or Google mainly focused on long video platform instead of the short video platform. A company called Musical.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mobile Payment Systems Case Study</title>
      <link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/zh/2020/10/01/mobile-payment-systems-case-study/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 22:25:19 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/zh/2020/10/01/mobile-payment-systems-case-study/</guid>
      <description>Mobile Payment Systems Why has China been an ideal environment to support mobile payment systems? Politically, payment licenses are controlled by government (relative financial institutions) and under strict regulation. So, tech giants like Alibaba who are qualified can increasingly develop their payment business in the early age. Plus, in the early stage of mobile payment, laws and rules are not so completed. Payment platform can utilize smart market strategies (like very high return rate) to attract more new potential users and enhance existing users’ engagement, which is effective in market expanding stage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New iPad Air 4 (2020) Presence by Apple Inc.</title>
      <link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/zh/2020/09/18/new-ipad-air-4-2020-presence-by-apple-inc./</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Sep 2020 01:25:19 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/zh/2020/09/18/new-ipad-air-4-2020-presence-by-apple-inc./</guid>
      <description>E-Commerce Presence Look Around New iPad Air 4 (2020) Presence by Apple Inc. Website Link
The iPad Air 4 (2020) got shown off at Apple&amp;rsquo;s September event held on September 16. There is a specific designed website (mobile version included) for this product. I&amp;rsquo;d like to do an analysis towards this very impressive E-Commerce presence.
Apple iPad Air product line is mainly targeted to educators/students, staffs and kids/teenagers. So, the most premium features this new product wants to convey to customers is its fancy appearance and powerful A14 Bionic for creation, study and entertainment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Puma Goes Omni Case Study</title>
      <link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/zh/2020/09/08/puma-goes-omni-case-study/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 23:30:19 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/zh/2020/09/08/puma-goes-omni-case-study/</guid>
      <description>Puma Goes Omni About Puma Puma Official Website
A Fancy Presentation
Slogan: &amp;ldquo;Run The Streets. Do You.&amp;rdquo;
The third largest sportswear manufacture in the world. (2018)
The company was founded in 1948 by Rudolf Dassler.
Building a Centralize Website Restructuring Strategy
 Replacing multiple e-commerce sites on different platform Unifying content and product strategies Building multiple teams in different regions, separate tasks  Content Management System (CMS)
&amp;ldquo;Database software program specifically designed to manage structures, unstructured data and objects in a Website environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>微信小程序云开发项目: 吃什么吖</title>
      <link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/zh/2020/04/05/%E5%BE%AE%E4%BF%A1%E5%B0%8F%E7%A8%8B%E5%BA%8F%E4%BA%91%E5%BC%80%E5%8F%91%E9%A1%B9%E7%9B%AE-%E5%90%83%E4%BB%80%E4%B9%88%E5%90%96/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2020 23:40:25 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/zh/2020/04/05/%E5%BE%AE%E4%BF%A1%E5%B0%8F%E7%A8%8B%E5%BA%8F%E4%BA%91%E5%BC%80%E5%8F%91%E9%A1%B9%E7%9B%AE-%E5%90%83%E4%BB%80%E4%B9%88%E5%90%96/</guid>
      <description>微信小程序云开发项目: 吃什么吖 项目GitHub 开发细节 太懒&amp;hellip;待更新 云开发功能 尝试了微信官方的云开发功能，无需自己部署服务器，且</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
